I'm just saying. At a certain point
in a woman's menstrual cycle...
Uh-uh. Oh.
(HR Woman:)You can't talk about that either.
(HR Woman:)Your language is entirely inappropriate,
and I'm going to advise...
(HR Woman:)...that you shut your mouth right now.
(Sheldon:)I don't see why I'm the one being
persecuted here.
Dr. Hofstadter was bragging about his
sexual desirability...
(Sheldon:)...to anyone who would listen.
Howard Wolowitz spent two years
using university resources...
(Sheldon:)...building a six-breasted sex robot.
(Sheldon:)And at the office Christmas party,
I heard Rajesh Koothrappali...
(Sheldon:)...refer to you several times
as "Brown Sugar."
Hofstadter, Wolowitz and
that last one was Rajesh Koothrappali?
Yes. But in his defense,
that wasn't racist. He's also brown.
(Leonard (singing):)I'm sorry Alex hit on me